

# KRISTINE ELAINE MONTOYA

INTERIOR DESIGNER

845.729.4769 | MONTOYA.KRISTINE@GMAIL.COM | KRISTINEMONTOYA.TUMBLR.COM

#### **PROFILE**

Experienced designer with a passion for discovering new ideas and innovative solutions to design problems. My inspiration of design comes from a multitude of things. From fashion to traveling, to art. I have a strong interest in designing and developing ambitious spaces that start a conversation.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **BFA INTERIOR DESIGN**

MICHAEL GRAVES COLLEGE KEAN UNIVERSITY Union, NJ | 2013 - 2017

#### **AAS LIBERAL ARTS IN MATH & SCIENCE**

ROCKLAND COMMUNITY COLLEGE Suffern, NY | 2011 - 2013

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE INTERIOR DESIGN INTERN

IMAGE CO DESIGN Garnerville, NY | Feb. 2016 - July 2016

Focused intern working in procurement. Ability to look for materials & finishes, meet with vendors, and create mood boards.

#### **PROCUREMENT OFFICER**

ICO DESIGN GROUP Garnerville, NY | July 2016 - Dec. 2016

To find quality goods or services at acceptable prices, while working with vendors. purchase orders, samples, budget costs and estimations. To assess financial performance of products and prepare specifications organized in spec books.

## PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT

**IKEA - LETS CHARETTE** 

MICHAEL GRAVES COLLEGE KEAN UNIVERSITY Elizabeth, NJ | April 2016

#### THINKING CREATIVELY

MICHAEL GRAVES COLLEGE KEAN UNIVERSITY Elizabeth, NJ | April 2016

#### **SHADOW A DESIGNER**

POSEN ARCHITECTS West Orange, NJ | March 2017

## SKILLS **AutoCAD** Revit Sketchup Microsoft Office Hand Rendering

## **ACKNOWLEDGEMENT**

GAGA EXHIBIT FOR THE ARTS

RAMAPO HIGHSCHOOL ART ASSOCIATION Garnerville, NY | April 2010

#### PERFORMING ARTISTIC TALENTS

RAMAPO HIGHSCHOOL AWARD CEREMONY Suffern, NY | June 2009

## **REFERENCES**

#### **ALAN HORWITZ**

ARCHITECT / PROFESSOR G3 Architecture 669 River Drive Elmwood Park NJ 07401 alahorwi@kean.edu

## BEKIR KELÇEOĞLU

INDUSTRIAL DESIGNER / PROFESSOR Syracuse University Syracuse, NY, 13210 Bkelceog@syr.edu

### **SHANY TELLER**

CEO DESIGNER Image Co Design 55 W. Railroad Avenue Garnerville, NY, 10923 shany@icodesigngroup.com (845) 593.1500

## **BLOG & INSPIRATION**

t tumblr.com/juukem